An Inventory of the Republican National Committee (U.S.) Opposition Research Group records
Hoover Institution Archives
Opposition Research Group records
1960-1984
85085
Republican National Committee (U.S.) Opposition Research Group.
64 Manuscript Boxes, 2 cubic foot boxes (27.5 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
The records include research materials accumulated and acquired by the Republican Opposition Research Group during the 1984 presidential election for use in the campaign against Democratic presidential candidates. The records consist of materials such as clippings, press releases, other printed matter, speeches, debate transcripts, memoranda, and video tapes regarding specific Democratic Party leaders such as Walter F. Mondale, John Glenn and Geraldine Ferraro, and specific political issues and special interest groups.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1985.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Related Materials
Ronald Reagan subject collection, Hoover Institution Archives
Ronald Reagan radio commentary sound recordings, Hoover Institution Archives
Historical Note
The Opposition Research Group operated as part of the Communications Division within the Republican National Committee, chaired by Michael Bayer. The group was formed "in 1984 with its own budget of $1.1 million, to create a master data bank of computerized voter research and opposition research. Staff amassed information on eight Democratic presidential candidates based on data from voting records, Congressional Record speeches, media clippings and transcripts, campaign materials, all of which was stored on a computer for easy access. In this way the party was able to track inconsistencies of its opponents and attack them. This original data base evolved into a network that linked information gleaned by Republicans in all 50 states, creating a master data base accessible to high-ranking Republican staff, even aboard Air Force One when Ronald Reagan was president."
Source:
J. M. Bayer & J. Rodota, "Computerized Opposition Research," Campaigns & Elections, 6, p. 26-27.
Scope and Content of Collection
The records include research materials accumulated and acquired by the Republican Opposition Research Group during the 1984 presidential election for use in the campaign against Democratic presidential candidates. The records consist of materials such as clippings, press releases, other printed matter, speeches, debate transcripts, memoranda, and video tapes regarding specific Democratic Party leaders, such as Walter F. Mondale, John Glenn and Geraldine Ferraro, and specific political issues and special interest groups.
Materials contain information about the Democratic Party presidential and vice-presidential nominees, Walter Mondale and Geraldine Ferraro, including speeches, financial information, and political background and history.
Also present are the records generated by the Opposition Research Group regarding its work, including materials regarding the Republican National Committee's innovative electronic research database and communications system, Voices for Victory, which allowed key members of the Republican Party to maintain constant communication and disseminate information quickly and efficiently regardless of geographic location.
Materials are arranged as they were received from the creator. Materials such as clippings files are arranged chronologically, while other files are arranged alphabetically by topic. Topical folder names created by the organization have been retained.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Mondale, Walter F., 1928-; Glenn, John, 1921-; Ferraro, Geraldine.; Reagan, Ronald.; Democratic Party (U.S.); Presidents--United States--Election 1984.
Collection Contents
- Walter Mondale realated materials, 1969-1984 (Box 1-39)
  Includes candidate notebooks, speeches, financial records, voting records, campaign literature, and information regarding Mondale's positions and past actions regarding specific issues. The bulk of the materials are Mondale candidate notebooks, which contain photocopies of clippings and other materials related to his political career. Arranged by format
  - Candidate notebooks, 1969-1984 (Folder 1-30)
    - 1984 November (Folder 1: 1)
    - 1984 October 23-31 (Folder 1: 2)
    - 1984 October 16-22 (Folder 1: 3)
    - 1984 October 8-15 (Folder 1: 4)
    - 1984 October 1-7 (Folder 1: 5)
    - 1984 September 22-24 (Folder 2: 1)
    - 1984 September 23-27 (Folder 2: 2)
    - 1984 September 27-30 (Folder 2: 3)
    - 1984 September 18-21 (Folder 2: 4)
    - 1984 September 14-17 (Folder 2: 5)
    - 1984 September 10-13 (Folder 2: 6)
    - 1984 September 7-9 (Folder 3: 1)
    - 1984 September 4-6 (Folder 3: 2)
    - 1984 September 1-3 (Folder 3: 3)
    - 1984 August 23-28 (Folder 3: 4)
    - 1984 August 22-24 (Folder 3: 5)
    - 1984 August 19-23 (Folder 3: 6)
    - 1984 August 16-19 (Folder 3: 7)
    - 1984 August 12-15 (Folder 4: 1)
    - 1984 August 7-12 (Folder 4: 2)
    - 1984 August 3-7 (Folder 4: 3)
    - 1984 August 1-3 (Folder 4: 4)
    - 1984 July 28-31 (Folder 4: 5)
    - 1984 July 23-28 (Folder 4: 6)
    - 1984 July 20-23 (Folder 4: 7)
    - 1984 July 19-20 (Folder 4: 8)
    - 1984 July 19 (Folder 4: 9)
    - 1984 July 17-18 (Folder 5: 1)
    - 1984 July 15-16 (Folder 5: 2)
    - 1984 July 13-15 (Folder 5: 3)
    - 1984 July 12-13 (Folder 5: 4)
    - 1984 July 7-11 (Folder 5: 5)
    - 1984 July 4-7 (Folder 5: 6)
    - 1984 July 3 (Folder 5: 7)
    - 1984 July 2 (Folder 5: 8)
    - 1984 July 1 (Folder 5: 9)
    - 1984 June 29-30 (Folder 5: 10)
    - 1984 June 28 (Folder 5: 11)
    - 1984 June 27 (Folder 5: 12)
    - 1984 June 25-26 (Folder 6: 1)
    - 1984 June 24 (Folder 6: 2)
    - 1984 June 22-23 (Folder 6: 3)
    - 1984 June 21 (Folder 6: 4)
    - 1984 June 19-20 (Folder 6: 5)
    - 1984 June 18 (Folder 6: 6)
    - 1984 June 15-17 (Folder 6: 7)
    - 1984 June 13-14 (Folder 6: 8)
    - 1984 June 11-12 (Folder 6: 9)
    - 1984 June 9-10 (Folder 6: 10)
    - 1984 June 8 (Folder 6: 11)
    - 1984 June 5-7 (Folder 6: 12)
    - 1984 June 4-5 (Folder 6: 13)
    - 1984 June 1-4 (Folder 6: 14)
    - 1984 June 1 (Folder 6: 15)
    - 1984 May 28-31 (Folder 7: 1)
    - 1984 May 24-27 (Folder 7: 2)
    - 1984 May 21-24 (Folder 7: 3)
    - 1984 May 16-20 (Folder 7: 4)
    - 1984 May 12-16 (Folder 7: 5)
    - 1984 May 11-12 (Folder 7: 6)
    - 1984 May 7-10 (Folder 7: 7)
    - 1984 May 3-7 (Folder 7: 8)
    - 1984 May 1-3 (Folder 7: 9)
    - 1984 April 28-30 (Folder 8: 1)
    - 1984 April 26-28 (Folder 8: 2)
    - 1984 April 24-25 (Folder 8: 3)
    - 1984 April 21-24 (Folder 8: 4)
    - 1984 April 16-20 (Folder 8: 5)
    - 1984 April 13-16 (Folder 8: 6)
    - 1984 April 11-13 (Folder 8: 7)
    - 1984 April 8-10 (Folder 8: 8)
    - 1984 April 5-8 (Folder 9: 1)
    - 1984 April 4-5 (Folder 9: 2)
    - 1984 April 2-3 (Folder 9: 3)
    - 1984 April 1-2 (Folder 9: 4)
    - 1984 March 29-31 (Folder 9: 5)
    - 1984 March 28-29 (Folder 9: 6)
    - 1984 March 27-28 (Folder 9: 7)
    - 1984 March 25-26 (Folder 9: 8)
    - 1984 March 23-25 (Folder 9: 9)
    - 1984 March 22-21 (Folder 10: 1)
    - 1984 March 20-21 (Folder 10: 2)
    - 1984 March 19-20 (Folder 10: 3)
    - 1984 March 19 (Folder 10: 4)
    - 1984 March 17-18 (Folder 10: 5)
    - 1984 March 15-17 (Folder 10: 6)
    - 1984 March 15 (Folder 10: 7)
    - 1984 March 14 (Folder 10: 8)
    - 1984 March 13 (Folder 10: 9)
    - 1984 March 12-13 (Folder 11: 1)
    - 1984 March 12 (Folder 11: 2)
    - 1984 March 11 (Folder 11: 3)
    - 1984 March 10-11 (Folder 11: 4)
    - 1984 March 9-10 (Folder 11: 5)
    - 1984 March 7-8 (Folder 11: 6)
    - 1984 March 6-7 (Folder 11: 7)
    - 1984 March 6 (Folder 11: 8)
    - 1984 March 4-5 (Folder 11: 9)
    - 1984 March 2-4 (Folder 12: 1)
    - 1984 March 1-2 (Folder 12: 2)
    - 1984 March 1 (Folder 12: 3)
    - 1984 February 27-29 (Folder 12: 4)
    - 1984 February 24-27 (Folder 12: 5)
    - 1984 February 23-24 (Folder 12: 6)
    - 1984 February 23 (Folder 12: 7)
    - 1984 February 22 (Folder 12: 8)
    - 1984 February 20-21 (Folder 12: 9)
    - 1984 February 19-20 (Folder 13: 1)
    - 1984 February 19 (Folder 13: 2)
    - 1984 February 17-18 (Folder 13: 3)
    - 1984 February 17 (Folder 13: 4)
    - 1984 February 16-17 (Folder 13: 5)
    - 1984 February 15 (Folder 13: 6)
    - 1984 February 14-15 (Folder 13: 7)
    - 1984 February 13-14 (Folder 13: 8)
    - 1984 February 12-13 (Folder 14: 1)
    - 1984 February 11 (Folder 14: 2-3)
    - 1984 February 10-11 (Folder 14: 4)
    - 1984 February 9-10 (Folder 14: 5)
    - 1984 February 7-9 (Folder 14: 6)
    - 1984 February 5-6 (Folder 14: 7)
    - 1984 February 3-4 (Folder 14: 8)
    - 1984 February 1-3 (Folder 15: 1)
    - 1984 January 29-31 (Folder 15: 2)
    - 1984 January 27-29 (Folder 15: 3)
    - 1984 January 26-27 (Folder 15: 4)
    - 1984 January 22-25 (Folder 15: 5)
    - 1984 January 20-22 (Folder 15: 6)
    - 1984 January 18-20 (Folder 15: 7)
    - 1984 January 16-17 (Folder 15: 8)
    - 1984 January 14-16 (Folder 16: 1)
    - 1984 January 10-13 (Folder 16: 2)
    - 1984 January 8-9 (Folder 16: 3)
    - 1984 January 5-8 (Folder 16: 4)
    - 1984 January 3-5 (Folder 16: 5)
    - 1984 January 1-3 (Folder 16: 6)
    - 1984 Miscellaneous (Folder 16: 7-8)
    - 1983 December (Folder 16: 9, Folder 17: 1-5)
    - 1983 November (Folder 17: 6-10)
    - 1983 October (Folder 18: 1-6)
    - 1983 September (Folder 18: 7-9)
    - 1983 August (Folder 19: 1-3)
    - 1983 July (Folder 19: 4-8)
    - 1983 June (Folder 19: 9)
    - 1983 June (Folder 20: 1-2)
    - 1983 May (Folder 20: 3-4)
    - 1983 April (Folder 20: 5-6)
    - 1983 March (Folder 20: 7)
    - 1983 February (Folder 20: 8-10)
    - 1983 January (Folder 21: 1-2)
    - 1982 November-December (Folder 21: 3)
    - 1982 October (Folder 21: 4)
    - 1982 July-September (Folder 21: 5)
    - 1982 April-June (Folder 21: 6)
    - 1982 February-March (Folder 21: 7)
    - 1982 January (Folder 21: 8)
    - 1981 February-December (Folder 21: 9)
    - 1981 January (Folder 21: 10)
    - 1980 November-December (Folder 22: 1)
    - 1980 October (Folder 22: 2)
    - 1980 September (Folder 22: 3)
    - 1980 July-August (Folder 22: 4)
    - 1980 April-June (Folder 22: 5)
    - 1980 January-March (Folder 22: 6)
    - 1979 November-December (Folder 22: 7)
    - 1979 September-October (Folder 22: 8)
    - 1979 July-August (Folder 23: 1)
    - 1979 April-June (Folder 23: 2)
    - 1979 January-March (Folder 23: 3)
    - 1978 September-December (Folder 23: 4)
    - 1978 July-August (Folder 23: 5)
    - 1978 May-June (Folder 23: 6)
    - 1978 March-April (Folder 23: 7)
    - 1978 January-February (Folder 23: 8)
    - 1977 October-December (Folder 23: 9)
    - 1977 August-September (Folder 24: 1)
    - 1977 July (Folder 24: 2)
    - 1977 June (Folder 24: 3)
    - 1977 April-May (Folder 24: 4)
    - 1977 February-March (Folder 24: 5)
    - 1977 January (Folder 24: 6)
    - 1976 November-December (Folder 24: 7)
    - 1976 October (Folder 24: 8-9)
    - 1976 September (Folder 25: 1)
    - 1976 August (Folder 25: 2)
    - 1976 July (Folder 25: 3-5)
    - 1976 June (Folder 25: 6)
    - 1976 May (Folder 25: 7)
    - 1976 April-January (Folder 25: 8)
    - 1975 September-December (Folder 26: 1)
    - 1975 June-August (Folder 26: 2)
    - 1975 March-May (Folder 26: 3)
    - 1975 January-February (Folder 26: 4)
    - 1975, Accountability of Power: Towards a Responsible Presidency (Folder 26: 5-6)
      Photocopies
    - 1974 November-December (Folder 26: 7)
    - 1974 October (Folder 26: 8)
    - 1974 September (Folder 26: 9)
    - 1974 June-August (Folder 27: 1)
    - 1974 April-May (Folder 27: 2)
    - 1974 January-March (Folder 27: 3)
    - 1973 November-December (Folder 27: 4)
    - 1973 September-October (Folder 27: 5)
    - 1973 June-August (Folder 27: 6)
    - 1973 May (Folder 27: 7)
    - 1973 April (Folder 27: 8)
    - 1973 January-March (Folder 27: 9)
    - 1972 December-October (Folder 27: 10)
    - 1972 August-September (Folder 28: 1)
    - 1972 June-July (Folder 28: 2)
    - 1972 April-May (Folder 28: 3)
    - 1972 January-March (Folder 28: 4)
    - 1971 December (Folder 28: 5)
    - 1971 November (Folder 28: 6)
    - 1971 September-October (Folder 28: 7)
    - 1971 June-August (Folder 28: 8)
    - 1971 May (Folder 28: 9)
    - 1971 April (Folder 28: 10)
    - 1971 March (Folder 29: 1)
    - 1971 January-February (Folder 29: 2)
    - 1970 December (Folder 29: 3)
    - 1970 August-November (Folder 29: 4)
    - 1970 July (Folder 29: 5)
    - 1970 May-June (Folder 29: 6)
    - 1970 March-April (Folder 29: 7)
    - 1970 January-February (Folder 29: 8)
    - 1969 November-December (Folder 29: 9)
    - 1969 October-September (Folder 30: 1)
    - 1969 August (Folder 30: 2)
    - 1969 April-May (Folder 30: 3)
    - 1969 January-March (Folder 30: 4)
    - 1968 March-December (Folder 30: 5)
    - 1968 January-February (Folder 30: 6)
    - 1967 August-December (Folder 30: 7)
    - 1967 January-July (Folder 30: 8)
    - 1966 January-November (Folder 30: 9)
    - 1960-1965 (Folder 30: 10)
  - Speeches and writings, 1975-1984 (Folder 31)
    - 1976 (Folder 31: 1-4)
    - 1977-1981 (Folder 31: 5)
    - 1982 (Folder 31: 6)
    - 1983 (Folder 31: 7-10)
    - Mondale's speech at the Democratic National Convention accepting the party's nomination, 1984 July 26 (Folder 31: 11)
  - Campaign literature, circa 1980s (Folder 32: 1-2)
  - Mondale/Ferraro campaign literature, circa 1980s (Folder 32: 3-4)
  - Mondale attack themes, circa 1980s (Folder 32: 5, Folder 33: 1)
  - Schedule, 1984 April-May (Folder 33: 2-3)
  - Voting records and related, 1965-1976 (Folder 33-34)
    - Voting records, 1965-1976 (Folder 33: 4, Folder 34: 1-4)
    - Mondale Senate votes, 1974-1976 (Folder 34: 5)
    - Mondale Congressional Quarterly, 1968-1975 (Folder 34: 6-7)
  - Republican National Committee reports regarding Mondale, 1975-1984 (Folder 35-36)
    - Mondale briefing book for Congresswoman Lynn Martin, 1984 September 12 (Folder 35: 1-2)
    - Mondale quotebook, undated (Folder 35: 3)
    - The Mondale report, circa 1984 (Folder 35: 4)
    - The Mondale travel report, 1980 (Folder 35: 5)
    - Weekly update on Mondale/Ferraro Campaign, 1984 September 30 (Folder 35: 6)
    - Letters to Mondale collected from the Lyndon Johnson Library, 1964-1968 (Folder 35: 7)
    - Letters to Mondale collected from the Gerald Ford Library, 1975 (Folder 35: 8)
    - Mondale Fact Book Vice President Malaise Twenty Years of Walter Mondale, 1984 (Folder 36: 1)
  - Issues and Talking Points, circa 1970s-1980s (Folder 36-39)
    Arranged alphabetically by topic
    - Abortion, circa 1970s-1980s (Folder 36: 2)
    - Acid rain, 1984 (Folder 36: 3)
    - Agriculture, circa 1984 (Folder 36: 4)
    - Aid to the poor, circa 1984 (Folder 36: 5)
    - Allies, 1984 (Folder 36: 6)
    - Amorality foreign policy, circa 1984 (Folder 36: 7)
    - Apology, 1984 (Folder 36: 8)
    - Arms control, circa 1984 (Folder 36: 9)
    - Attacks, 1984 (Folder 36: 10)
    - Balanced Budget, circa 1984 (Folder 36: 11)
    - Budget spending, circa 1984 (Folder 36: 12)
    - Carter connection and disagreement, 1980; 1984 (Folder 36: 13)
    - Central America, 1984 (Folder 36: 14)
    - Central Intelligence Agency (CIA), 1984 (Folder 36: 15)
    - Chemical and biological weapons, circa 1984 (Folder 36: 16)
    - Children/families, circa 1984 (Folder 36: 17)
    - China, circa 1984 (Folder 36: 18)
    - Civil rights, circa 1984 (Folder 36: 19)
    - Conventional forces, circa 1984 (Folder 36: 20)
    - Crime, circa 1984 (Folder 36: 21)
    - Cuba, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 1)
    - Defense spending, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 2)
    - Deficits, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 3)
    - Democratic criticism, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 4)
    - Deregulation, 1984 (Folder 37: 5)
    - Disclosure, 1984 (Folder 37: 6)
    - Draft and registration, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 7)
    - Drugs, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 8)
    - Education, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 9)
    - Elitist, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 10)
    - Energy, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 11)
    - Environment, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 12)
    - Fear Mongering, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 13)
    - Federalism, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 14)
    - Flip-flops, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 15)
    - Foreign aid, 1984 (Folder 37: 16)
    - Gay rights, 1984 (Folder 37: 17)
    - Grenada mission, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 18)
    - Growth, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 19)
    - Gun control, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 20)
    - Health, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 21)
    - Housing, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 22)
    - Human rights, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 23)
    - Hunger, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 24)
    - Immigration, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 25)
    - Industrial policy, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 26)
    - Inflation, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 27)
    - Infrastructure, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 28)
    - Interest rates, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 29)
    - Isolationism, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 30)
    - Israel, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 31)
    - Issues research, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 32)
    - Leadership, circa 1984 (Folder 37: 33)
    - Lebanon, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 1)
    - Liar, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 2)
    - Malaise, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 3)
    - Military aid, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 4)
    - Military reform, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 5)
    - Mondale the mean, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 6)
    - Naïve foreign policy, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 7)
    - NATO/Japan, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 8)
    - Northern Ireland, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 9)
    - Nuclear energy, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 10)
    - Nuclear forces, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 11)
    - PAC contributions, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 12)
    - Past v. future, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 13)
    - Persian Gulf, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 14)
    - Politician, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 15)
    - Pork barrel, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 16)
    - Prediction, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 17)
    - Quitter, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 18)
    - Romania, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 19)
    - School prayer, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 20)
    - Social Security, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 21)
    - Soviet threat, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 22)
    - Soviet Union, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 23)
    - Space-based defense, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 25)
    - Special interests, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 24)
    - Staff/advisors, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 26)
    - Stupid remarks, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 27)
    - Tainted delegates, circa 1984 (Folder 38: 28)
    - Talking points, 1984 (Folder 38: 29)
    - Taxes, circa 1984 (Folder 39: 1)
    - Terrorism, circa 1984 (Folder 39: 2)
    - Third World, circa 1984 (Folder 39: 3)
    - Trade, circa 1984 (Folder 39: 4)
    - Traditional values, circa 1984 (Folder 39: 5)
    - Unemployment/jobs, circa 1984 (Folder 39: 6)
    - Unspecified big spending plans, circa 1984 (Folder 39: 7)
    - Waste, fraud, and abuse, circa 1984 (Folder 39: 8)
    - Wish v. reality, circa 1984 (Folder 39: 9)
    - Women, circa 1984 (Folder 39: 10)
    - Veterans, circa 1984 (Folder 39: 11)
    - Victim of circumstances, circa 1984 (Folder 39: 12)
  - Financial information, 1981-1984 (Folder 39)
    - Tax returns, 1981-1983 (Folder 39: 13-15)
    - Tax returns, miscellany, 1984 (Folder 39: 16)
- Geraldine Ferraro materials, 1978-1984 (Box 39-45)
  Consists of candidate notebooks, financial records, congressional history, and information regarding Ferraro's positions and actions regarding specific issues. Also includes materials regarding her husband John Zaccaro and his financial information. The bulk of the materials are Ferraro's candidate notebooks, which contain photocopies of clippings and other materials related to her political career. Arranged by format
  - Candidate notebooks, 1978-1984 (Folder 40-43)
    - 1978 (Folder 40: 1)
    - 1979 (Folder 40: 2)
    - 1980 (Folder 40: 3)
    - 1981 (Folder 40: 4)
    - 1982 (Folder 40: 5)
    - 1983 (Folder 40: 6)
    - 1984 January-February (Folder 40: 7)
    - 1984 March-April (Folder 41: 1)
    - 1984 May-June (Folder 41: 2)
    - 1984 July 1-15 (Folder 41: 3-4)
    - 1984 July 16-31 (Folder 41: 5-6)
    - 1984 August 1-14 (Folder 42: 1-2)
    - 1984 August 15-31 (Folder 42: 3-4)
    - 1984 September 1-14 (Folder 42: 5-6)
    - 1984 September 15-30 (Folder 43: 1)
    - 1984 October (Folder 43: 2-3)
    - 1984 November (Folder 43: 4)
  - Biography, family information, and 1978 campaign literature, circa 1980s (Folder 43: 5)
  - My Name Is Geraldine Ferraro by Lee Michael Katz, 1984 (Folder 43: 6)
    Paperback volume
  - Speeches, 1978-1984 (Folder 44: 1)
  - Financial documents, undated (Folder 44: 2)
  - Congressional bills sponsored, circa 1979-1984 (Folder 44: 3)
  - Congressional committee overview, 1984 (Folder 44: 4)
  - Committee to Elect Ferraro 9th Congressional District, New York, circa 1978 (Folder 44: 5)
  - House disbursements, 1979-1984 (Folder 44: 6)
  - House disclosures, 1979-1984 (Folder 44: 7)
  - Spending and Taxing votes, circa 1979-1984 (Folder 44: 8)
  - Tape transcripts, 1978 October-November (Folder 44: 9-10)
    See also Audiovisual file
  - Attack themes, issues, and talking points materials, circa 1984 (Folder 45)
    Arranged in chronological order
    - Abortion, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 1)
    - Aid to the poor, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 2)
    - Allies, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 3)
    - Arms control, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 4)
    - Attack themes, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 5)
    - Budget/spending, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 6)
    - Central America, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 8)
    - Children and families, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 7)
    - Crime and justice, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 9)
    - Defense and foreign policy, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 10)
    - Defense budget, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 11)
    - Deficits, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 12)
    - Disclosure, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 13)
    - Domestic issues, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 14)
    - Editorials, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 15)
    - Education and school prayer, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 16)
    - Employment/jobs, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 17)
    - Energy, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 18)
    - Environment, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 19)
    - Far East, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 20)
    - Finance and ethics, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 21)
    - Foreign aid, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 22)
    - Gun control, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 23)
    - Housing, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 24)
    - Human rights, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 25)
    - Hunger and nutrition, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 26)
    - Inflation, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 27)
    - Infrastructure, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 28)
    - Middle East, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 29)
    - Nuclear forces/conventional weapons, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 30)
    - Press appearances, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 31)
    - Social security, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 32)
    - Soviet Union, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 33)
    - Special interests, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 34)
    - Terrorism, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 35)
    - Women's rights, circa 1984 (Folder 45: 36)
  - Miscellany, circa 1979-1984 (Folder 45:37)